Guide to the Oliver F. Atkins photograph collection, 1943-1975
George Mason University Libraries
- Series 3: Negatives, Contact Sheets, Slides, 1945-1975; (45 boxes)
  - Subseries 3.2: Alphabetical, 1945-1975; (34.5 boxes)
    - Hagerty, James, March 1960 (Box 79, Folder 9)
    - Halaby, Najeeb, December 1964 (Box 79, Folder 10)
    - Hall, Len, 1950s (Box 79, Folder 11)
    - Hanson, John, December 1956 (Box 79, Folder 12)
    - Hapgood, Charles, October 1958 (Box 79, Folder 13)
    - Harriman, W. Averell, September 1963 (Box 79, Folder 14)
    - Harte, Vance, June 1966 (Box 79, Folder 15)
    - Hatcher, Andrew, August 1961 (Box 79, Folder 16)
    - Hatfield, Mark, May 1967 (Box 80, Folder 1)
    - Healey, Paul, 1960s (Box 80, Folder 2)
    - Herter, Christian, August 1959, January 1960 (Box 80, Folder 3)
    - Hoffa, Jimmy, 1954-1962 (Box 80, Folder 4)
    - Hoffa, Jimmy, 1959-1962 (Box 80, Folder 5)
    - Hoffa, Jimmy, 1959-1962 (Box 80, Folder 6)
    - Hokkaido Tribe, 1951 (Box 80, Folder 7)
    - Humphrey, Hubert, March 1959 (Box 80, Folder 8)
    - Humphrey, Hubert, August 1964 (Box 80, Folder 9)
    - Humphrey, Hubert, September 1964 (Box 80, Folder 10)
    - Humphrey, Hubert, September 1964 (Box 81, Folder 1)
    - Humphrey, Hubert and Edmund Muskie, Democratic National Convention, 1968 (Box 81, Folder 2)
    - India, November-December 1962 (Box 81, Folder 3)
      1 of 4
    - India, November-December 1962 (Box 81, Folder 4)
      2 of 4
    - India, November-December 1962 (Box 81, Folder 5)
      3 of 4
    - India, November-December 1962 (Box 81, Folder 6)
      4 of 4
    - Indiana Polling, 1959 (Box 81, Folder 7)
    - Internal Revenue Service, February 1965 (Box 82, Folder 1)
    - Jackson, Henry, August 1960 (Box 82, Folder 2)
    - Jackson, Mahalia, September 1959 (Box 82, Folder 3)
    - Jail in Washington, D.C., 1950s (Box 82, Folder 4)
    - Jazz Festival in Washington, D.C., June 1962 (Box 82, Folder 5)
    - Jencks, Christopher, January 26, 1965 (Box 82, Folder 6)
    - Johnson, Lady Bird, December 1963 (Box 82, Folder 7)
    - Johnson, Lady Bird, December 1962-June 1964 (Box 82, Folder 8)
    - Johnson, Lady Bird, May 1965 (Box 82, Folder 9)
    - Johnson, Lady Bird, April 1968 (Box 82, Folder 10)
    - Johnson, Jacqueline, August 1966 (Box 82, Folder 11)
    - Johnson, Lyndon B., 1950s (Box 83, Folder 1)
      Includes Jacqueline Kennedy
    - Johnson, Lyndon B., 1960s (Box 83, Folder 2)
    - Johnson, Lyndon B., 1960s (Box 83, Folder 3)
      Lyndon B. Johnson with military
    - Johnson, Lyndon B., 1961-1962 (Box 83, Folder 4)
      1 of 2
    - Johnson, Lyndon B., 1961-1962 (Box 83, Folder 5)
      2 of 2
    - Johnson, Lyndon B., 1963-1965 (Box 83, Folder 6)
    - Johnson, Lyndon B., 1963-1967 (Box 83, Folder 7)
    - Johnson, Lyndon B., December 1963-January 1968 (Box 83, Folder 8)
      color slides 1
    - Johnson, Lyndon B., December 1963-June 1964 (Box 83, Folder 9)
      color slides 2
    - Johnson, Lyndon B., December 1963-March 1968 (Box 84, Folder 1)
      color slides 3
    - Johnson, Lyndon B., December 1963-June 1967 (Box 84, Folder 2)
      color slides 4
    - Johnson, Lyndon B., December 1963-January 1967 (Box 84, Folder 3)
      color slides 5
    - Johnson, Lyndon B., December 1963-January 1968 (Box 85, Folder 1)
      color slides 6
    - Johnson, Lyndon B., December 1963-June 1964 (Box 85, Folder 2)
      Meetings, public events
    - Johnson, Lyndon B., 1964 (Box 85, Folder 3)
    - Johnson, Lyndon B., 1964 (Box 85, Folder 4)
      Election
    - Johnson, Lyndon B., May 1964 (Box 85, Folder 5)
      Church near the Lyndon B. Johnson Ranch
    - Johnson, Lyndon B., May 1964 (Box 85, Folder 6)
    - Johnson, Lyndon B., November 1964 (Box 85, Folder 7)
    - Johnson, Lyndon B., July 23, 1965 (Box 85, Folder 8)
    - Johnson, Lyndon B., 1965 (Box 86, Folder 1)
      Oval Office
    - Johnson, Lyndon B., January 1965 (Box 86, Folder 2)
    - Johnson, Lyndon B., March 1965 (Box 86, Folder 3)
    - Johnson, Lyndon B., July 1966 (Box 86, Folder 4)
      Ranch
    - Johnson, Lyndon B., July 1966 (Box 86, Folder 5)
      Omaha, Nebraska, Des Moines, Iowa, Lyndon B. Johnson ranch
    - Johnson, Lyndon B., June 1967 (Box 86, Folder 6)
      Glassboro, New Jersey; Alexei Kosygin
    - Johnson, Lyndon B., June 1967 (Box 86, Folder 7)
    - Joint Chiefs of Staff and Civilian Secretaries, March 1964 (Box 86, Folder 8)
      Maxwell Taylor, Robert S. McNamara, George W. Ball, John McCone, Jack Valenti
    - Jones, Grover, 1966 (Box 86, Folder 9)
    - Kahn, Robert, 1960s (Box 86, Folder 10)
    - Keats, John, 1967 (Box 86, Folder 11)
    - Kelso (Horse), December 1963 (Box 86, Folder 12)
    - Kennedy Brothers, 1955-1963 (Box 86, Folder 13)
    - Kennedy, John F., 1940s (Box 87, Folder 1)
    - Kennedy, John F., 1945-1967 (Box 87, Folder 2)
    - Kennedy, John F., 1950s (Box 87, Folder 3)
    - Kennedy, John F., 1953-1957 (Box 87, Folder 4)
      Saturday Evening Post stories about John F. Kennedy; 4x5 negatives
    - Kennedy, John F., 1956 (Box 87, Folder 5)
    - Kennedy, John F., 1960 (Box 87, Folder 6)
    - Kennedy, John F., 1960 (Box 87, Folder 7)
    - Kennedy, John F., 1960 (Box 87, Folder 8)
    - Kennedy, John F., 1960 (Box 87, Folder 9)
    - Kennedy, John F., 1960-1961 (Box 87, Folder 10)
    - Kennedy, John F., 1960-1963 (Box 87, Folder 11)
    - Kennedy, John F., 1960-1963 (Box 88, Folder 1)
    - Kennedy, John F., 1960-1963 (Box 88, Folder 2)
    - Kennedy, John F., August 1960 (Box 88, Folder 3)
    - Kennedy, John F., 1961 (Box 88, Folder 4)
    - Kennedy, John F., 1961-1963 (Box 88, Folder 5)
    - Kennedy, John F., March 1961 (Box 88, Folder 6)
    - Kennedy, John F., May 1961 (Box 88, Folder 7)
    - Kennedy, John F., June 1961 (Box 88, Folder 8)
    - Kennedy, John F., 1963 (Box 88, Folder 9)
    - Kennedy, John F., 1963 (Box 89, Folder 1)
    - Kennedy, John F., 1963 (Box 89, Folder 2)
      Funeral, Arlington National Cemetery
    - Kennedy, John F., November 1964 (Box 89, Folder 3)
      Arlington National Cemetery
    - Kennedy, Robert F., 1950s (Box 89, Folder 4)
    - Kennedy, Robert F., 1960s (Box 89, Folder 5)
    - Kennedy, Robert F., 1963-1968 (Box 89, Folder 6)
    - Kennedy, Robert F., 1968 (Box 89, Folder 7)
    - Kennedy, Robert F., 1968 (Box 89, Folder 8)
    - Kennedy, Robert F., 1968 (Box 89, Folder 9)
    - Kennedy, Ted, September 1962 (Box 89, Folder 10)
    - Khrushchev, Nikita, September 1959 (Box 90, Folder 1)
    - Kilpatrick, James, February 1968 (Box 90, Folder 2)
    - Kirk, Claude, March 1967 (Box 90, Folder 3)
    - Korean War, March-April 1921 (Box 90, Folder 3)
    - Korean War, 1951 (Box 90, Folder 4)
    - Korean War, 1951 (Box 90, Folder 5)
    - Korean War, 1951 (Box 90, Folder 6)
    - Ku Klux Klan, December 1965 (Box 90, Folder 7)
    - Labor Leaders, 1960 (Box 91, Folder 1)
    - Labor Leaders, 1962-1967 (Box 91, Folder 2)
    - Lady Put that Casserole Away, 1949 (Box 91, Folder 3)
    - Lapp, Ralph, March 1968 (Box 91, Folder 4)
    - Las Vegas on the Potomac, June 1957 (Box 91, Folder 5)
    - Life Extension Society, February 1966 (Box 91, Folder 6)
    - Lippman, Walter, September 1960 (Box 91, Folder 7)
    - Lincoln, Evelyn, August 1965 (Box 91, Folder 8)
    - Little Room that Saves Lives, 1957 (Box 91, Folder 9)
    - Long, Russell, 1965 (Box 91, Folder 10)
    - M-16 Auto Rifle, January 29, 1968 (Box 91, Folder 11)
    - MacArthur, John D., January 1965 (Box 91, Folder 12)
    - Mansfield, Mike, November 1961 (Box 91, Folder 13)
    - Marshall, Thurgood, 1960s (Box 91, Folder 14)
    - Matancero Mystery Solved, June 1960 (Box 91, Folder 15)
    - Mathy, Sonny, December 1966 (Box 91, Folder 16)
    - Mayfield, Rufus "Catfish", January 1968 (Box 91, Folder 17)
    - McCarthy, Eugene, December 1967 (Box 91, Folder 18)
    - McCarthy, Joe, 1950 (Box 91, Folder 19)
    - McCone, John, October 1961 (Box 91, Folder 20)
    - McCormack, John, December 1963 (Box 91, Folder 21)
    - McNamara, Robert S., 1960s (Box 91, Folder 22)
    - McNamara, Robert S., May 1964 (Box 91, Folder 23)
    - McNamara, Robert S., 1965-1966 (Box 92, Folder 1)
    - Medicare, February 1965 (Box 92, Folder 2)
    - Mesta, Perle, July 1965 (Box 92, Folder 3)
    - Military and Weapons Demonstrations, 1950s (Box 92, Folder 4)
    - Miller, William, September 1962 (Box 92, Folder 5)
    - Millionaires Article, January 1965 (Box 92, Folder 6)
    - Millionaires Article, 1965 (Box 92, Folder 7)
    - Mink, Patsy, May 10, 1965 (Box 92, Folder 8)
    - Minoso, Minnie, April 1954 (Box 92, Folder 9)
    - Mitchell, James P., 1950s (Box 92, Folder 10)
    - Mona Lisa at the National Gallery of Art, January 16, 1963 (Box 93, Folder 1)
    - Money Men, October 26, 1967 (Box 93, Folder 2)
      White House and Congressional budget meetings and hearings
    - Morphine Substitute, October 1960 (Box 93, Folder 3)
    - Morton, Thruston B., January 17, 1968 (Box 93, Folder 4)
    - Moses, Faye and Hugo Zacchini, May 1962 (Box 93, Folder 5)
    - Montgomery, Ruth and Jean Dixon, April 1965 (Box 93, Folder 6)
    - Moyers, Bill, 1965 (Box 93, Folder 7)
    - Murphy, George, 1967 (Box 93, Folder 8)
    - Murray, Mary, 1956 (Box 93, Folder 9)
    - Murrow, Edward R., August 6, 1962 (Box 93, Folder 10)
    - Muskie, Edmund S., 1957 (Box 93, Folder 11)
    - NASA, 1961-1964 (Box 93, Folder 12)
      Ranger, Saturn, Mercury
    - National Bureau of Standards and Pershing Ballistic Missiles, June-July 1960 (Box 93, Folder 13)
    - New Zealand, January 1963 (Box 93, Folder 14)
      1 of 3
    - New Zealand, January 1963 (Box 94, Folder 1)
      2 of 3
    - New Zealand, January 1963 (Box 94, Folder 2)
      3 of 3
    - Nicklaus, Jack, February 1961 (Box 94, Folder 3)
    - Nixon, Patricia, 1972-1973 (Box 94, Folder 4)
    - Nixon, Richard M. and John F. Kennedy, 1950s-1960s (Box 94, Folder 5)
    - Nixon, Richard M., 1950s-1970s (Box 94, Folder 6)
      4x5 negatives
    - Nixon, Richard M., 1952 (Box 94, Folder 7)
      I Can Say He's a Wonderful Guy
    - Nixon, Richard M., 1953 (Box 94, Folder 8)
    - Nixon, Richard M., 1953 (Box 94, Folder 9)
    - Nixon, Richard M., May 1958 (Box 94, Folder 10)
    - Nixon, Richard M., August 1958 (Box 94, Folder 11)
    - Nixon, Richard M., September 1960 (Box 94, Folder 12)
    - Nixon, Richard M., May 1960 (Box 95, Folder 1)
    - Nixon, Richard M., March 6, 1974 (Box 95, Folder 2)
    - Nixon's My Boss, 1957 (Box 95, Folder 3)
      Rose Mary Woode
    - North Carolina, May 1958 (Box 95, Folder 4)
    - Oak Ridge National Laboratory, January 1963 (Box 95, Folder 5)
    - Oyster Industry in the Chesapeake Bay, September 1957 (Box 95, Folder 6)
    - Patent Office Feature, 1950s (Box 95, Folder 7)
    - Pentagon under Robert S. McNamara, November 1962 (Box 95, Folder 8)
    - Pearson, Drew, 1956 (Box 95, Folder 9)
    - Percy, Charles H., 1966 (Box 95, Folder 10)
    - Personal and Family, 1950s (Box 96, Folder 1)
    - Phillips, Maggie and William, July 1965 (Box 96, Folder 2)
    - Photographer's Gallery, 1950s (Box 96, Folder 3)
    - Picketing, 1950s-August 16, 1961 (Box 96, Folder 4)
    - Picketing the Soviet Embassy to protest invasion of Czechoslovakia, August 1968 (Box 96, Folder 5)
    - Picketing the White House to protest atomic atmospheric testing, December 1961 (Box 96, Folder 6)
    - Pill That Hates Salt, August 1957 (Box 96, Folder 7)
      Hospitals
    - Pilots released by Soviets, January 1961 (Box 96, Folder 8)
    - Pity the Poor School Superintendent, May 1954 (Box 96, Folder 9)
    - Political Figures, 1950s (Box 96, Folder 10)
      Adlai Stevenson, Eleanor Roosevelt, Winston Churchill, Richard M. Nixon, Bernard Montgomery, Harry S. Truman, John Foster Dulles
    - Political Figures, January 1953 (Box 96, Folder 11)
      Alben W. Barkley, Harry S. Truman, Estes Kefauver, Leverett Saltonstall, John F. Kennedy, Albert Gore, Sr.
    - Political Figures, January 1953 (Box 96, Folder 12)
      John Foster Dulles, Charles Erwin Wilson, Robert Taft
    - Pope Paul IV and Lyndon B. Johnson, January 1965 (Box 96, Folder 13)
    - Prince Edward County Free Schools, August 1964 (Box 96, Folder 14)
    - President's Guest House, August 1960 (Box 96, Folder 15)
      Blair House
    - Presidential Campaign Debates, September 1960s (Box 96, Folder 16)
      John F. Kennedy, Richard M. Nixon
    - Presidential Campaign Debates, October 1960 (Box 96, Folder 17)
    - Protocol School, January 1966 (Box 96, Folder 18)
    - Pumpkin Papers, September 8, 1975 (Box 96, Folder 19)
    - Queen Mary, September 1967 (Box 96, Folder 20)
    - Railroads Fight Back, August 1959 (Box 96, Folder 21)
    - Reed, David, 1966 (Box 96, Folder 22)
    - Reedy, George, June 1965 (Box 96, Folder 23)
    - Red Cross Washington, D.C. chapter, 1962 (Box 96, Folder 24)
    - Republican Personalities, 1950s-1960s (Box 96, Folder 25)
    - Reston, Virginia, April 22, 1968 (Box 96, Folder 26)
    - Ribicoff, A. A., Case of the Candid Congressman, April 1952 (Box 96, Folder 27)
    - Rickover, Hyman G., 1950s (Box 97, Folder 1)
    - Rickover, Hyman G., 1953 (Box 97, Folder 2)
    - Rickover, Hyman G., 1957 (Box 97, Folder 3)
    - Ridder, Walter, May 1961 (Box 97, Folder 4)
    - Riggs National Bank Annual Report Photographs, 1973-1974 (Box 97, Folder 5)
      Some images may have been created in the 1950s; 1 of 2
    - Riggs National Bank Annual Report Photographs, 1973-1974 (Box 97, Folder 6)
    - Riot Training, 1960s (Box 97, Folder 7)
    - Roberts, Nan, May 25, 1965 (Box 97, Folder 8)
    - Rockefeller, Nelson, 1950s (Box 97, Folder 9)
    - Rockefeller, Nelson, September 1958 (Box 97, Folder 10)
    - Rockwell, Norman, February 1960 (Box 97, Folder 11)
    - Rogers, William P., November 1949 (Box 97, Folder 12)
    - Romney, George, 1957 (Box 97, Folder 13)
    - Romney, George, July 19, 1957 (Box 98, Folder 1)
    - Rooney, John J., July 1958 (Box 98, Folder 2)
    - Roosevelt, James, August 1959 (Box 98, Folder 3)
    - Rosenberg Demonstrations, February 1953 (Box 98, Folder 4)
    - Rubenstein, Richard, December 30, 1965 (Box 98, Folder 5)
    - Rusk, Dean, May 1961 (Box 98, Folder 6)
    - Rusk, Dean, May 1964 (Box 98, Folder 7)
    - Russell, Richard B., January 23, 1965 (Box 98, Folder 8)
    - Russian Embassy, May 1958 (Box 98, Folder 9)
    - Santa Maria, 1966 (Box 98, Folder 10)
    - Saturday Evening Post Staff in Washington, D.C., January 20, 1964 (Box 98, Folder 11)
    - Sayre, Francis B., Jr., June 1963 (Box 98, Folder 12)
    - Scranton, William W., June 12, 1964 (Box 98, Folder 13)
    - Seagrave, Sterling, May 10, 1965 (Box 98, Folder 14)
    - Senators, June 1965-June 1968 (Box 98, Folder 15)
    - Senate Appropriations Committee, October 1963 (Box 98, Folder 16)
    - Senate Foreign Relations Committee, February 1966 (Box 98, Folder 17)
    - Senate Labor Hearing, 1950s (Box 98, Folder 18)
    - Senate Office Building, July 1959 (Box 99, Folder 1)
    - Senate Restaurant, 1950 (Box 99, Folder 2)
    - Sevareid, Eric, March 1959 (Box 99, Folder 3)
    - Shaw, Carolyn Hagner, March 1959 (Box 99, Folder 4)
    - Smith, Beverly W., Jr., May 1957 (Box 99, Folder 5)
      Saturday Evening Post writer
    - Smith, Margaret Chase, October 1948, January 1964 (Box 99, Folder 6)
    - Smith, Steven, July 1963 (Box 99, Folder 7)
    - Sorenson, Ted, January 16, 1964 (Box 99, Folder 8)
    - Sorenson, Ted, 1960 (Box 99, Folder 9)
    - So the Customer Is Always Right, 1957 (Box 99, Folder 10)
      Macy's New York City
    - Space and Science Reports and Hearings, 1950s (Box 99, Folder 11)
    - State Department Building, 1960s (Box 99, Folder 12)
    - Steeves, David, July 1957 (Box 99, Folder 13)
    - Stephens, Tom, June 1958 (Box 99, Folder 14)
    - Stewart, Jimmy, March 1960 (Box 99, Folder 15)
    - Stinnett, Caskie, 1960s (Box 99, Folder 16)
    - Submarine Missile Story, January 1958 (Box 99, Folder 17)
    - They Suit The Big Shots, June 1959 (Box 100, Folder 1)
      T. I. Swartz and Sons
    - Turner, Walter M., September 1962 (Box 100, Folder 2)
    - Television Antennas, October 1961 (Box 100, Folder 3)
    - Tydings, Joseph D., May 1967 (Box 100, Folder 4)
    - Symington, Stuart S., March 1960 (Box 100, Folder 5)
    - Tree, Marietta P., July 1960 (Box 100, Folder 6)
    - Tree Saving, 1960s (Box 100, Folder 7)
    - Truman, Harry, March 11, 1950 and undated (Box 100, Folder 8)
    - Truman, Margaret, 1946 (Box 100, Folder 9)
    - Truth Machine, February-March, 1975 (Box 100, Folder 10)
    - Udall, Stuart, March 1965 (Box 100, Folder 11)
    - Undertaker's Story, May 1961 (Box 100, Folder 12)
    - Unidentified, 1950s-1960s (Box 100, Folder 13)
    - Unitas, Johnny, September-October 1958 (Box 100, Folder 14)
    - United States Capitol Building, 1959 (Box 100, Folder 15)
    - United States Capitol Building, 1960s (Box 100, Folder 16)
    - United States Capitol Building and Dome, 1962 (Box 100, Folder 17)
      Includes images of construction
    - United States Capitol Building National Statuary Hall, 1950s-1960s (Box 100, Folder 18)
    - United States Supreme Court steps and crowds, 1950s (Box 100, Folder 19)
    - United States Supreme Court, October 1962 (Box 101, Folder 1)
    - United States Supreme Court, August 1967 (Box 101, Folder 2)
    - United States Supreme Court, August 1967 (Box 101, Folder 3)
    - Unknown Soldier Ceremony at United States Capitol Building, 1950s (Box 101, Folder 4)
    - Unknown Soldiers from the Korean War Interment, May 28-30, 1958 (Box 101, Folder 5)
    - U.N.'s Five-Ring Circus, May 1950 (Box 101, Folder 6)
    - Valachi, Joe, October 1963 (Box 101, Folder 7)
    - Veecle, Bill, August 1963 (Box 101, Folder 8)
    - Vinson, Carl, November 1964 (Box 101, Folder 9)
    - Vorenburg, James, December 1966 (Box 101, Folder 10)
    - Wallace, George, March 1965 (Box 101, Folder 11)
      Includes Lyndon B. Johnson
    - Washington, D.C. scenes, October-November 1961, February 1967 (Box 101, Folder 12)
    - Washington D.C. area scenes, June 1968 (Box 101, Folder 13)
      National Mall, Pentagon, United States Supreme Court Building, Pan American Building
    - Washington, D.C. views of the United States Capitol and State Department buildings, October 1961 (Box 101, Folder 14)
    - Washington, George, will and documents, 1947 (Box 101, Folder 15)
    - Washington File, 1955 (Box 101, Folder 16)
    - Washington File, 1955 (Box 102, Folder 1)
    - Watson, Marvin, March 1967 (Box 102, Folder 2)
    - Weather Research Story, August 1958 (Box 102, Folder 3)
    - Westmoreland, William C., April 1967 (Box 102, Folder 2)
    - Wheeler, Earl, August 1963 (Box 102, Folder 3)
    - White House, 1960s (Box 102, Folder 4)
    - White House Dogs, 1970s (Box 102, Folder 5)
    - White House Space Problem, 1950s (Box 102, Folder 6)
    - Wilderness, 1959 (Box 102, Folder 7)
    - Williams, Edward B., 1962 (Box 102, Folder 8)
    - Williams, John J., March-April 1964 (Box 102, Folder 9)
    - Wisher, Mr. and Mrs. Frank, May 1965 (Box 102, Folder 10)
    - Women for Peace, 1962 (Box 102, Folder 11)
    - Women's Christian Temperance Union, November 23, 1965 (Box 102, Folder 12)
    - Women's Peace March, January 1968 (Box 102, Folder 13)
    - World War II, ca. 1943 (Box 102, Folder 14)
      American Red Cross, Tunisia, Italy
    - Wounded Vietnam War Veterans, December 1966-January 1967 (Box 102, Folder 15)
    - Yugoslavia Assignment, April 1963 (Box 102, Folder 16)
- Series 4: Personal Papers, Exhibit Images, and Nature Photography, 1940s-1974; (5 boxes)
  Series 4 contains correspondence, awards, press travel packets, copies of images for exhibits and reference use, and a photograph assignment on the Shenandoah Valley in Virginia. Note that there is also correspondence and notes throughout the folders in the Series 3.
  - Copy Negatives, Eisenhower, Dwight D., 1950s (Box 103, Folder 1)
  - Copy Negatives, Dancers, Yugoslavia, North Africa, March on Washington, 1940s-1960s (Box 103, Folder 2)
  - Copy Negatives, Kennedy, John F., 1950s-1960s (Box 103, Folder 3)
  - Copy Negatives, Kennedy, Robert F., 1960s (Box 103, Folder 4)
  - Copy Negatives, Presley, Elvis, and Richard M. Nixon, December 18, 1970 (Box 103, Folder 5)
  - Copy Negatives, Truman, Harry S., 1940s-1950s (Box 103, Folder 6)
  - Copy Prints, Dancers, 1940s (Box 103, Folder 7)
  - Copy Prints, Forrestal, James, 1940s (Box 103, Folder 8)
  - Copy Prints, Kennedy, Jacqueline, 1950s (Box 103, Folder 9)
  - Copy Prints, Kennedy, John F., 1960s (Box 103, Folder 10)
    Jacqueline Kennedy, Caroline Kennedy, John Kennedy, Jr., Pierre Salinger
  - Copy Prints, Kennedy, John F. and Robert F., 1950s-1960s (Box 103, Folder 11)
  - Copy Prints, Kennedy, Robert F., 1960s (Box 103, Folder 12)
  - Copy Prints, King, Martin Luther, Jr., 1960s (Box 103, Folder 13)
  - Copy Prints, Naples, Italy, World War II, 1940s (Box 103, Folder 14)
  - Copy Prints, Space and Science Reports, 1950s (Box 103, Folder 15)
  - Copy Prints, Streisand, Barbara, 1960s-1970s (Box 103, Folder 16)
  - Copy Prints, Truman, Harry, S., 1940s-1950s (Box 103, Folder 17)
  - Copy Slides, Nixon, Richard M., 1950s-1970s (Box 103, Folder 18)
  - Copy Slides, Truman, Harry S., 1940s-1950s (Box 103, Folder 19)
  - Correspondence, Donovan, Robert, 1961 (Box 103, Folder 20)
  - Correspondence, Kennedy, John F. Inauguration, 1960-1961 (Box 103, Folder 21)
  - Correspondence, Kennedy Library, 1964 (Box 103, Folder 22)
  - Correspondence, Miscellaneous, 1960s-1970s (Box 103, Folder 23)
  - Correspondence, Nixon Library Foundation, 1973-1975 (Box 103, Folder 24)
  - Correspondence, Nixon Library Requests, 1974 (Box 103, Folder 25)
  - Correspondence, Nixon White House, 1969-1974 (Box 103, Folder 26)
  - Correspondence, Pat Nixon Book, 1973 (Box 103, Folder 27)
  - Correspondence, "Photographic Impressions of the Presidency" Exhibit, 1972 (Box 103, Folder 28)
  - Correspondence, Saturday Evening Post, 1961-1967 (Box 103, Folder 29)
  - Correspondence, White House Photographer/Nixon Photographer, 1970s (Box 103, Folder 30)
  - Shenandoah Valley, Correspondence, 1970s (Box 104, Folder 1)
  - Shenandoah Valley, Negatives, 1970s (Box 104, Folder 2)
  - Shenandoah Valley, Prints, Contact Sheets, 1970s (Box 104, Folder 3)
  - Press Notes, Richard M. Nixon Visit to Austria and Soviet Union, May 1972 (Box 104, Folder 4)
  - Press Notes, Richard M. Nixon Visit to Iran and Poland, May-June 1972 (Box 104, Folder 5)
  - Press Notes, Richard M. Nixon Visit to Europe, September 27-October 5, 1970 (Box 104, Folder 6)
  - Press Notes: Richard M. Nixon Visit to China, February 1972 (Box 104, Folder 7)
  - Press Notes: Richard M. Nixon Visit to China, February 1972 (Box 104, Folder 8)
    Includes memorabilia
  - Publications, First Monday, 1971-1972 (Box 105, Folder 1)
  - Publications, Government Photography, March 1972 (Box 105, Folder 2)
  - Publications, The Inaugural Book, 1973 (Box 105, Folder 3)
  - Publications, Miscellaneous Articles, 1960s-1970s (Box 105, Folder 4)
  - Publications, The Nixon Yearbook, 1968 (Box 105, Folder 5)
  - Publications, The Nixon Years: Lift of Leadership, 1972 (Box 105, Folder 6)
  - Publications, Saturday Evening Post, 1960s-1970s (Box 105, Folder 7)
  - Publications, Summons to Greatness, 1972 (Box 105, Folder 8)
  - Publications, Partners, 1972 (Box 105, Folder 9)
  - Publications, The President's Trip to China, 1972 (Box 105, Folder 10)
  - Awards and Recognitions, 1970s (Box 106, Folder 1)
  - Photograph Captions, 1950s (Box 106, Folder 2)
  - Photograph Captions, 1950s (Box 106, Folder 3)
  - Photograph Captions, 1950s (Box 106, Folder 4)
  - Publications, Elector, Reflector, 1968, 1972 (Box 106, Folder 5)
  - Publications, Life, December 29, 1972 (Box 106, Folder 6)
  - Publications, Ladies Home Journal, July 1972 (Box 106, Folder 7)